The heat wave that is said to be once in a decade continues across the country.
This hot season, which has broken the record for the hottest day ever recorded in central Tokyo, is the perfect time for a cold ice cream!
This year marks the 50th anniversary of the arrival of ice cream from the U.S. to Japan, and the number of flavors created so far is more than 1,300!
31 ice cream boasts the largest number of stores in the industry with more than 1,300 flavors.
When I was in high school, there was a 31 near my school.
I used to go there often with my friends.
Every year for my birthday, I always get an ice cream cake from 31.
It's called "Happyness Box".
And they have a Happyness Box that comes with a 31 scoop and a horn.
It also comes with a horn and a scoop of 31.
What's that? You can do 31 at home?
That's right.
I want to try it.
Can I go?
Home? Excuse me.
Why are you doing this?
Tonight, we're going to use 31 Ice Cream's top 20 flavors...
We're going to have an apple contest.
You two can only choose seven times.
If you can line up all the apple cards in a row, horizontally, vertically, diagonally, and anywhere in between, you've won.
The rankings are based on annual sales in the year 2022.
The year 2022?
You weren't here in that year?
What's with that reaction?
Times change, maybe the number of units people buy has changed.
Like high school kids in 2012.
Seven items or less. 31 gift certificates worth 10,000 yen.
I'm so happy!
And if we can get the first four items straight and the apples are in the basket, we'll get a donation.
Yay!
10,000 yen.
Oh, my God, it's that hard.
I wonder if these guys won't make it when they get this from the other side.
Especially these two.
I see.
Let's show them this anyway.
Okay.Ok.
But then again, we're such good classmates...
I think I'm going to have to shut up.
What the hell?
Asahi mercilessly chastises Momota, but...
No...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Among the top 20 31 most popular flavors ranked this time
31's unique ice cream flavors such as Popping Shower, fruity flavors like melon and orange-strawberry, chocolate flavors, as well as Jamka coffee and rum coffee.
There are also 7 flavors such as Jamka Coffee, Rum Raisin, Chocolate Mint, and many more!
Let's see which one we should aim for first.
I guess I should start with the easiest to guess.
That's the pattern, right?
I'll do it the other way around.
So we'll start with the highest ranked ones that are easy to guess.
New pattern
If you open up that area, you've already narrowed it down, haven't you?
That's right.
Wow, that's smart.
Smart.
Clever.
A little clever.
Wait, you've never said that to me before in your life.
You.
But I really wanted to put myself out there somewhere.
The real me.
Here.
I want to come out.
By the way, out of all of these, how about this one, this one that I think I can guess the number for?
No, I think this is the absolute top... hopping shower... is definitely number one.
I know, I love kids!
I think I can open the top spot.
Which is your favorite flavor?
Jamka coffee.
I'm sorry, out of all my friends, this is the first time I've had Jamka Coffee.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.Wait a minute. You're kidding.
Wait a minute.
Of course it's delicious.
I really think that Jamka coffee is chocolate.
Oh...
And this...
I'm sorry... can we change it?
Why?
And it's...
Yummy, yummy, yummy!
And there's a Jamucca Almond Fatch, which is Jamucca coffee with a little bit of chocolate in it.
It sounds delicious.
It's so good!
I've never had it.
I'm thinking strawberry cheesecake and cookies and cream.
I think they're at the top of the list.
I think they're at the top of the list, too.
I see.
So can I have a Jamka coffee once?
On the contrary.
I'd like to see how many people like Carabo.
To be honest, it's easier to find a place where the first and second places are.
Let's say 13th.
I'd appreciate it if it was number 13.
There's 999.
I can't guess 9 and 13.
It's not easy.
It would be great if you could guess that.
Oh, my God, that's Jamka coffee.
Let's do this one time.
Here it comes.
Okay, Jamka Coffee!
Momota's strategy was to go with Jamka Coffee's 9th guess instead of the top one.
It's nice to meet you.
What? But I'm so happy to see you here.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Let's go meet new people!Let's go meet new people!
Thank you.
Duh.
Yeah, it's good.
No, it's good.
No, it's just like this.
It's like milk coffee, but in a milk bottle.
Coffee milk.
It's sweeter, mellow, a little milky.
Not too thick.
You can have another one.
You can mix it with ice cream.
Yeah.
It's like you can make it all together and eat it.
I see.
Yeah, you've thought of that, too.
You're smart.
So, yeah, the real you is a little...
I can see it, can't I?
I think it's about time.
I wonder if it'll come at the right time.
Isn't it?
He's so smart.
Yeah, it is.
Let's see the results.
Momota predicted Jamuka Coffee to finish 9th.
Please!
Please, Kanako!
Yes!
First place
17th place
Wow, but...
No
Just barely.
Maybe a little bit, but I can shut up beyond this point.
I can shut up from here on out.
I knew it.I knew it.
I don't know why.
That's what it's all about, isn't it?
I know, I know, I know.
There you go.
But thank you.
It's hard to guess 17.
Three, six, one is easier.
I think he's here.
I'll take it from here.
I'll go from there.
My guess was wrong, but Momota's strategy worked.
I was able to vacate the lower positions.
That leaves us with 1st, 3rd and 6th.
That leaves us with 1st, 3rd, and 6th, which are easy to predict.
And now...
What about this?
I'm not sure I should start with number one.
Fourth place, or maybe first place already.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's always open.
I got 10 tickets up for grabs.
No, I'm going. Popping then.
No, I'm not going.
Did you notice there's a popping shower
Did you notice there's a popping shower next door?
What? - Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wait a minute... am I that much of a pain in the ass?
I'm having a popping shower today. No, I just thought I was feeling a little icky today.
I thought you were popping showers today. I'm popping kanako today.
Popping Kanako predicted Popping Shower to be No. 1.
I haven't had popping showers in a long time.
I'm so excited... let's read it once before we eat it.
I don't need it.
Don't eat it yet.
Bon appétit!Bon appétit!
Popping Shower originally appeared in 2000 under the name Millennium
Really? That's right.
It was a limited edition flavor for 3 months, but it became so popular that they ran out of ingredients in just 2 weeks!
After that, it became a standard flavor and is always on the shelves.
They did that, didn't they?
When people were calling for it.
I haven't had it in a while, but it's really good.
It's a crackling candy!
It's delicious!
What is this green mint?
It's not like chocolate mint mint.
It's not that strong.
You're 31?
Thank you for everything.
Suddenly I'm happy.
I predicted popping showers as number one, but what do you think?
Second place.
First place!
Yay!
I knew it, but I guess you're right. How long has this been No. 1?
For a long time.
About 15 years.
Oh, wow.
I knew it.
Good.
I'm so happy.
Now, if we can combine 3rd and 6th place, we'll get 100,000 yen.
Can you apple it without making a mistake?
Third place is a lot harder than I thought.
No, second place is still possible.
What's second place?
It's not strawberry cheesecake.
I'm thinking third.
Oh, this...
Strawberry cheesecake.
Oh, but I think you're right.Oh, but maybe so.
I knew it. Strawberry cheesecake is also a big cheesecake in this ice cream.
It's like a big cheesecake.
There's something special about it, isn't there?
Love Potion 31 is the same.
You can only get this feeling at 31.
There's a lot of it in there.
It's more than you think.
And the caramel ribbon...
I know... it's hard to get rid of.
I think it's a battle for second and third place.
We've had this for a while, and the caramel ribbon.
But you know what?
Strawberry Cheesecake.
It cost 100,000 yen.
And 200,000 yen for the two of them combined.
It should be more popular.
No, no, no, 100,000 yen for the two of us.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
That's unacceptable.
There it is. There it is.
I don't care if it's 100,000 yen.
I said 100,000 yen.
Then you should have written 50,000 yen.
It's 100,000 yen!
No, I've already won.
What'll it be?
I don't know.
I'll go with my first hunch.
You'd be surprised how often you get it right the first time.
It's okay.
Okay.
Strawberry cheesecake.
I want some.
Yeah, I want some.
Let's do it.Yup.
Strawberry Cheesecake, which Asahi says she usually eats, is predicted to come in third place.
What was the result?
I'm so happy!
You know how there are people you can't forget?
It's like that, isn't it?
I don't know.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
There's a lot of cheesecake in there.
Yes, it's good.
And this strawberry sauce in it.
It's sweet and sour.
It's really good.
Wow, it's delicious!
If it's #3 or #6, it's a reach!
What is the ranking of Strawberry Cheesecake?
No. 1
Which one is it?
Sixth.
Wow!
Wait, wait, wait.
What? You found this pattern?
I didn't think it was a lock.
What? You really guessed next?
Yeah, I did.
What? I told you, didn't I?
No way.
You're serious?
The two of us.
Two.
No way. Sixth place is up for grabs, and we're all in.
Then you guess third place, and bingo.
You just won your first 100,000 yen.
Good luck with that.
So, what are you going to do for me?So, what should we ask for out of these three?
Asahi and Momota's third place candidates were these three types
Oh, caramel!
Caramel ribbon.
Cookies.
The caramel ribbon is really good, too.
But there are some people who can't eat caramel.
Cookies or berry berry?
How about cookies?
I'd have to say second place.
How fun is this?
Isn't it?
I always thought berry-berries were different.
Not berries, because everyone already loves strawberries.
But since it's number two, I'm inclined to go with the cookie-ac-cream.
No. 3, berry berry, I did more.
Cookies.
Okay, let's go with cookies.
Finally, Asahi predicted Cookie Amecream and bed.
Wow. This is good.
Because there's more in there than you think.
It's really crunchy.
Look at all this.
Look at this!
Look at the chunks!
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy.
Yeah, it's good.
Yum.
These cookies are really satisfying.
It's got a lot of cookies in it.
The texture is really good, isn't it?
Cookies come in various sizes so that you can enjoy the texture.
That's for sure.
You can enjoy the crunchy texture of cocoa cookies of different sizes.
I can see why.
When the waiter makes them for me.
where there are a lot of big parts.I want it to be made in a place where there are lots of big places.
I'd like to see it made in a place where there are lots of big places.
I'd like it there, please.
Of course.
Yes, please.
I'm so excited!
It's the first time I've done this.
I think my heart is going to jump out of my chest right here.
If Cookies & Cream comes in third.
I'll be the first person in history to win 100,000 yen!
What do you think?
Fifth place
Fifth place.
Too close to call!
Wow so...
And it's heavy!
Too frustrating! I could have made it!
You could have made it!
I could have finished 3rd!
Too bad! But if I get a bingo in the next 3 rounds, I get 10,000 yen!
Which one will come in third place?
Let's take a look at the rest of the lineup!
There are 31 unique items such as Love Potion and Caramel Ribbon, as well as
Fruity and chocolatey flavors such as muskmelon and strawberry
Rum Raisin and Chocolate Mint are also left!
You have three more chances to win! If you win within the next three times, you'll get 10,000 yen!
Let's go! Let's go, Caramel Limon!
Let's go!
Wait, let's start with Berry Berry.
Was it berry-berry?
That's right.
Let's go with Berry Berry.
But Kanako chose Very Berry Berry.
What do you mean?
It means we're in 14th place.
No Berry Berry.
Because you said earlier that Jamooka Coffee was 9th, but now it says it's 17th.I mean, I just said Jamoca Coffee was #9, and now it's #17.
I mean, seriously, I love it, but it's berry, berry, strawberry.
It's okay. I'll go once.
I'll go one time.
Let's go to Berry Berry Berry once.
There's still time for three more.
All right, let's go Berry, Berry, Berry, Strawberry.
I'll be shocked if I win this one.
I'll be shocked
Momota had always predicted Berry Berry Strawberry to come in third place!
I wonder what the number will be...
Oh, what?
Mosquito meat
What? Was it this big?
Look at the mosquito meat!
Oh, it's so big!
Bon appétit!
I'm feeling more confident now.
Delicious!
Mmm, delicious!
I've never had ice cream that you can feel the strawberries like this!
And the strawberries are so crispy, it's delicious.
Yes, this is Berry Berry Strawberry.
Rich strawberry milk ice cream with strawberry puree and pulp.
Strawberry puree and pulp in a rich strawberry milk ice cream!
In English, there are two kinds of berries, one with a V and the other starting with a B.
and the berry that starts with "B".
Oh, and berry berry!
Very strawberry, indeed!
Very Strawberry Strawberry
That's a trivia. I didn't know that.
Can you pronounce it?
Berry, berry.
Berry good.
Thank you.
Berry, berry, berry.
Berry-berry-berry
Berry BerryBerry Berry
Strawberry
I didn't know this.
Momota predicted Berry Berry Strawberry as #3
I'd like to win a 10,000 yen gift certificate and eat ice cream all the time now that the heat wave continues, but...
No. 1
As it turns out...
What?
Third place!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
Oh my god!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
That sucks.
Why is it the worst?
Because you just made me want to look like you.
Cookie or belly belly?
Berry Berry? Because everyone already likes strawberry.
But if I want to be like you, I'll be like cookies or cream.
Did you do more berries?
Let's go with cookies.
Okay, let's do cookies.
Seriously?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I was just about to grab them for real.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's a good one.
House.
This is a reflection.
It's a reflection.
It's so frustrating.
Oh, thank God.Good.
Then you get 10,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
And here's your chance to double up.
Oh, what?
I'll have you play a game.
What's this?
We've only played this one already.
It's the one you're all familiar with.
It's really popular in Japan right now.
It's so popular in Japan!
It's so popular, it's a big hit in Tik-Tok.
I've never seen it.
Tik-Tok is a big no-no! Tik-Tok is a big no-no!
It's cute, isn't it?
It's fashionable.
Are you actually going to wear this?
Oh.
Ah!
I don't know any flowers with this.
A flower! Look at this.
Me, me? You wrote that?
It's elaborate. Here's what's going to happen.
You're right.
Flowers, flowers, flowers, flowers, flowers...
Two in a row, both of them.
If they both hit, it'll be like this.
Can we make 10,000 yen each with this?
Yes, why not?
Can you double up on the 10,000 yen gift certificate?
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready. - Poo!
I'm ready.
Wait a minute!
I know, right?
I took it forI took it for the
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm so low right now, I honestly didn't think I was going to make it.
I was so nervous.
Yeah, I know.
Just relax. You're gonna be fine.
Thank you so much.
That's great.
It was low, wasn't it?
I thought it was low here.
It's low here.
Mr. Awaatari.
No, it's great.
After this, I started to understand.
You're taller.
Oh, my God.
Look at your face.
Is it hard to do this, Kanako?
I'm getting a double-up chance.
It's on, so you have a chance to double up.
Wait a minute. I don't get it.
It's 10,000 yen difference.
No, it's impossible after such a great catch.
What could be better than that?
Thanks for the hit dance.
It's a head turner.
You better watch it, 'cause I'm gonna see it through to the end.
Okay, okay, I'll watch till the end.
I'll watch till the end.
Three, two, one.
It's a little backwards.
I like the sound.
I don't know if it's the bending or the bending or what.
It's like a tonneau.
It's like a silly tonneau.It's like a silly tonneau.
Nice.
She's laughing and crying.
Wait a minute.
Ok please.
I'm a eudanibe.
I'm a weekend heroine.
That's all, gently.
I'll take that heart of yours
I'll take it!
Yay!
We got it!
We've all been robbed.
They're all gone.
This one.
But you know what... we matched.
I've got it together.
I'm looking right at it.
Did it work?
Which way?
It worked.
That's great!
Very good.
Excellent.
It's a success.
You two!
You did it!
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy!
By the way, here are the top 20 most popular flavors of Martin 1 ice cream.
I hope you'll take a look at them!
Let's eat good ice cream and get over this heat wave!